Edwin Augustus Porcher Collection
Yale Center for British Art, Rare Books and Manuscripts
- Miscellaneous, Series III
  - Certificate, 1861 November 1; Blane, George, born 1813; 1 sheet (1 page): written in pen and black ink; 20.5 x 16.5 cm (Box Vol. 2, no. 11)
    Certificate signed by Commander George Blane testifying to Edwin Augustus Porcher's service as Lieutenant under command on the HMS Hibernia, from August 6, 1861, to November 1, 1861.
  - Envelope, 20th century; 1 envelope; 16.5 x 9.5 cm (Box Vol. 2, no. 12)
    A small manila envelope that once housed letters and fragments from the YCBA Porcher collection. Bears notes in red ink.
    Porcher, Edwin Augustus, 1824-1878